A Guide to the Stacy May papers FA442
Rockefeller Archive Center
Stacy May papers
1919-1972
1940-1965
Rockefeller Archive Center
May, Stacy (1896-1980)
FA442
40.54 Cubic Feet 28 legal-sized document boxes, 71 letter-sized document boxes, 1 half-legal-sized document box, and 1 oversized box
Related Materials
Rockefeller Foundation records Rockefeller Brothers Fund: Special Studies Project International Business Economic Corporation (IBEC) records Nelson A. Rockefeller papers Ford Foundation records
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as received by the Rockefeller Archive Center, in two subgroups.
Biographical / Historical
Stacy May was an economist who helped plan U. S. war production during World War II and who worked as an economic consultant to the Rockefeller family for several decades. He was born in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, on April 18, 1896 and attended Amherst College in Massachusetts. Between 1917 and 1919, he served with Motor Ambulance Co. 61 of the American Expeditionary Forces in World War I. After the war, May continued his studies and received his Ph.D. in economics jointly from Brookings Graduate School of Economics and Government (now Brookings Institute), and Washington University. Between 1921 and 1932, May taught economics at Amherst College, Cornell University, and Dartmouth College.
In 1932, he became Assistant Director of Social Sciences at Rockefeller Foundation, where he worked until 1942. Between 1940 and 1944, May was Director of the Bureau of Research and Statistics of the War Production Board and its predecessor agencies. In 1941, he went to Britain as special representative of Henry L. Stimson, U. S. Secretary of War, in an effort to combine and coordinate British and American war production programs.
Following World War II and a brief time as Assistant to the President of McGraw-Hill Publishing Company (1944-1946), May resumed his long association with the Rockefellers in 1947. He worked as an economic advisor to Room 5600 (the Rockefeller Family office), with IBEC – the International Basic Economy Corporation – and as an economic advisor to Nelson Rockefeller during his time as Governor of New York State and during his campaign for the U. S. presidency.
May also served as economic analyst for several government advisory committees and commissions, as well as serving for many years as a Member of the National Planning Association which had been founded in 1934 as a nonprofit, nonpolitical organization devoted to planning by Americans in agriculture, business, labor, and the professions.
Stacy May retired as an economic consultant to the Rockefellers in 1965. He died on November 24, 1980, at 84 years of age.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Stacy May papers were donated and transferred to the Rockefeller Archive Center by the American Heritage Center at Univerity of Wyoming (Laramie) in 2008.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents Stacy May's career as an economist and more particularly, as an economic consultant and advisor to the Rockefeller family. It includes personal letters, correspondence, papers, speeches, reports, bound reports, and publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
- Subgroup 1, 1919-1972; 1; 34.94 Cubic Feet 74 legal-sized document boxes, 1 oversized box
  Scope and Contents
  Subgroup 1 contains Stacy May's files from 1919-1972 and includes personal correspondence, letters, reports, speeches, newspaper clippings, articles, and publications. The material was originally organized into several alphabetical runs, and this order has been maintained, leading to some duplication of subject matter. Along with material from May's time with the War Production Board and with Nelson Rockefeller, Subgroup 1 also contains several folders relating to Cape Cod, Massachusetts, indicative of Stacy May's interest in this area where he spent his retirement years.
  - Addresses, Lectures and Speeches, 1940-1941, 1952-1953, 1958, 1961, 1969, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agendas, 1940, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Announcements, 1944, 1965, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Applications and Forms, 1943, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1940-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1904-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biographical Information - Stacy May, 1939, 1944, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Booklets, Brochures, Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1944, 1963, 1966, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Booklets, Brochures, Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1941, 1958, 1966, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Booklets, Brochures, Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1930, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Booklets, Brochures, Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1940, 1946, 1965, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Business Cards, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Charts, 1944-1946, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Charts, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - 1919-1939 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - 1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - 1943 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - 1944 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - 1945 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - 1946 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - 1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - 1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - 1952 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - 1953 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - 1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - 1956 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - 1957 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - 1958 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - 1958 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - 1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - 1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence - 1963 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence - 1965 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence - 1968 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence - 1971 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence - Incomplete or No Dates, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Directories, 1946, 1964, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Documentary Publications Nos. 1-3, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Documentary Publications Nos. 4-5, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 4-7, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 8-14, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 15-17, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 18-19, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 20-21, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 22-23, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 24-25, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Documents: Historical Reports on War Administration, War Production Board, Special Studies Nos. 26-27, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of Agriculture, 1963, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of Commerce, 1946-1947, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, U. S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Department of Labor, 1966-1968, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of Labor: Area Trends in Employment and Unemployment, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of Labor: Area Trends in Employment and Unemployment, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Documents: U. S. Department of State, 1944, 1946, 1962, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Documents: War College Instruction Circular, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Documents: U. S. Congressional Documents, 1946, 1963, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Documents: U. S. Documents - Various, 1940, 1946, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Documents: State Documents - Connecticut, Massachusetts, Oregon, 1947, 1960, 1961, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Documents: State Documents - New York, 1964, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Documents: State Documents - New York, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Documents: State Documents - New York, 1970, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Documents: State Documents - New York, 1971, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Documents: Foreign - Thailand, 1962, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Addresses, 1944-1946, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Addresses - Russian Material, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Advisory Committee on the Work Programme on Industrialization, February 4-13, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - African Affairs Society of America, Ltd., 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Agriculture, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Air University, War College, USAF, Maxwell Air Force Base, Alabama, May 23, 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - American Committee Luncheon, Kenneth Lindsay, June 27, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - American Committee on United Europe, 1953-1954, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - American Council on NATO, 1952-1962 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - America's New Opportunities in World Trade, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Arms Control, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - The Atlantic Council, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Atomic Information, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Atomic Scientists Bulletins, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - August-October Panel, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Automation, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Balance of Payments Conference, Princeton, New Jersey, November 16, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Banca Commerciale Italiana (Raffaele Mattioli), 1954-1957, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Barbara - Information Available Here, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Robert P. Bass, Jr., 1957-1962 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Berlin, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Boston Conference on Distribution, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Brazil - Stacy May Report, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Brussels Conference, May 30-June 2, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Budget, 1961, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Business Advisory Council - Department of Commerce, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 117)
  - Council of Economic Advisers Meeting, Washington, D.C., October 7, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Council of Economic Advisers-New York State/Council of Economic Advisers-U.S.A., October 1970 Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Central Economic and Demographic Study in New York State, Office of Planning Coordination, 1966, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Capitalist Manifesto, undated (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Ad Hoc Committee on the Communist Economic Offensive, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Chamber of Commerce of Greater Pittsburgh, "An Experiment in Practical Development Assistance in West Africa", May 18, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Chamber of Commerce of Greater Philadelphia, "International Regional Markets in 1959", January 7, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Foreign Commerce Department Committee, 1954-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Checchi and Company, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Chemical Report, "The Chemical Industry", 1954 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Chemical Report - Summary (to be placed on top of Report), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - Cincinnati Council on World Affairs, 1957-1960 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - Civil Defense, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Civil Rights, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Cleveland World Trade Association, November 16, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Coleman - OBE - Department of Commerce, undated (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy, Inc., Conference on Trade Policy, January 27-28, 1960, Washington, D.C., 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - Committee of 21, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 135)
  - Communications Satellites, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - The Communist Economic Challenge, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 137)
  - Conference on Tensions in Development in the Western Hemisphere - University of Bahia, Salvador, Brazil, August 6-12, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 138)
  - Conferences for Corporation Executives, School of Advanced International Studies, October 19, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 139)
  - Conservation Commission Meeting, March 12, 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence - 55th Street, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 141)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Committee on Studies, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 142)
  - Cuba, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 143)
  - Cuba - Stacy May Report, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 144)
  - Current Unemployment Rates and Prices - New York versus U. S. and California, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 145)
  - Current Work, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 146)
  - Debevoise, Plimpton & McLean, 1955-1956, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 147)
  - Defense, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 148)
  - Downtown Economists, "An Experiment in Practical Development Assistance in West Africa", May 3, 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - The Economic Development of Ecuador, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Economic Growth, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 151)
  - Economic Highlights of Regions of the U. S., 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 152)
  - "Economic Interest in Tropical Medicine", November 13, 1953, 1952-1954, 1956-1957, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 153)
  - Education, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 154)
  - The 87th Congress and the Kennedy Legislative Program, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 155)
  - Federal Revenue Sharing - National Industrial Conference Board, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Federal Wholesale Druggists' Association, Greenbrier Conference, September 1960 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Fifth Conference of the Industrial Council for Tropical Health, October 29, 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Folklore and Fact about Underdeveloped Areas, "Foreign Affairs" Quarterly Review, January 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - Ford Foundation, 1955-1956, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - Foreign Affairs, "Measuring the Marshall Plan", 1948 (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - Foreign Trade, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - 14th Annual Forecasting Conference, Chamber of Commerce of Greater Philadelphia, January 5, 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - Berent Friele, 1953, 1955-1964 (Box 25, Folder 164)
  - Godkin Lecture, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 165)
  - Goldberg Rebuttal - 9/30/70, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 166)
  - Goldwater, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 167)
  - Harvard Business School, Latin American Conference, September 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 168)
  - Health (Civil Medical Care), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 169)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1956 (Box 26, Folder 170)
  - IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation) - General, 1956-1964 (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation) - Kenaf, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 173)
  - International Bank, International Finance Corporation, International Monetary Fund, 1952-1962 (Box 28, Folder 174)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1956, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 175)
  - International Development Advisory Board - Correspondence, 1950-1952, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 176)
  - International Development Advisory Board - Partners in Progress, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 177)
  - Iran, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 178)
  - Ireland - Correspondence, 1950-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 179)
  - Irish Report - "Industrial Potentials of Ireland: An Appraisal", 1952 (Box 29, Folder 180)
  - Jacob K. Javits, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 181)
  - Japan, 1952, 1954-1956 (Box 29, Folder 182)
  - Jobs Turned In, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 183)
  - Kennedy Administration Actions - Domestic Topics, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 184)
  - Kennedy Administration Actions - Foreign Topics, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 185)
  - Kennedy's Economic Policies and Kennedy's Economists, 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 186)
  - "Keys to Latin American Development", August 29, 1952, New Orleans, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 187)
  - Walt Klein - Work on Value Added and Wage Rates, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 188)
  - Kuala Lumpur Conference, Council on World Tensions, February 23-29, 1964, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 189)
  - Labor, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 190)
  - Laos and Vietnam, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 191)
  - Latin America, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 192)
  - Latin American Pulp and Paper Industry, October 18-November 2, 1954, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 193)
  - Manufacturing Data, undated (Box 31, Folder 194)
  - Margaret Marsh, 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 195)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Carroll L. Wilson, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 196)
  - Stacy May - Miscellaneous, 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 197)
  - Stacy May - Notes on Talks, 1951-1954 (Box 31, Folder 198)
  - Stacy May - Personal, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 199)
  - Stacy May - Personal, 1946-1949, 1951-1952, 1955-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 200)
  - John J. McCloy - Foreign Aid Statements, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 201)
  - Mid-Century Conference on Resources for the Future, December 1953 - Documents (Box 32, Folder 202)
  - Mining and Metallurgical Society, January 25, 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 203)
  - Mount Desert, 1951-1957 (Box 33, Folder 204)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - American Newspaper Publishers Association, Remarks on European Policy, April 25, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 205)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Governor's Conference on Automation, June 1-3, 1960, Cooperstown, New York - "Accelerated Economic Growth: A Key to the American Future", June 1, 1960, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 206)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Cincinnati Statement, April 29, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 207)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Confederation, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 208)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Detroit Economic Club Speech, April 16, 1962 - "Is U. S. National Economic Policy Geared to 1962 and Future Needs?" (Box 34, Folder 209)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Executive Club Speech, Chicago, May 7, 1964 - "Foreign Trade Policy in a Changing World", 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 210)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - International Radio and Television Society, April 17, 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 211)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - "Tax Incentives for Growth and More Jobs Now", Statement Released to the Press at Milwaukee, Wisconsin, March 9, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 212)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Ministers of Foreign Affairs, Costa Rica, August 17, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 213)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - North American Newspaper Alliance Series, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 214)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Pan American Press Seminar, New Orleans, April 21, 1964 - Latin America Speech (Box 35, Folder 215)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Position Papers, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 216)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speech - Economics Club of New York, November 9, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 217)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speech - Minneapolis Junior Chamber of Commerce - Farm Speech, December 14, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 218)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speech - National Foreign Trade Council, November 18, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 219)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speech - New York City Board of Trade, October 8, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speeches - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960, 1962, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 221)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Statement - Balance of Payments, September 2, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 222)
  - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) - Topeka, Kansas and Omaha, Nebraska, April 5-6, 1963 - Press Release, "20 Million New Jobs: A Program for Growth", April 6, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 223)
  - NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Organization), 1962 (Box 36, Folder 224)
  - NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Organization) Parliamentarians - Economic Committee of the NATO Parliamentarians - The Economist Intelligence Unit, Ltd., 1958-1963 (Box 36, Folder 225)
  - National Planning Association - Projections, 1968, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 226)
  - National Planning Association - United Fruit, 1954-1958 (Box 37, Folder 227)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research - Advisory Committee on Study of Tax Policies for Economic Growth, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 228)
  - National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 229)
  - National Economy Speech II, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 230)
  - National Foreign Trade Council, Inc. - The Americas Luncheon, November 17, 1958, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 231)
  - National Security Resources Board, 1948-1950, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 232)
  - Natural Resources, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 233)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 234)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 235)
  - New England Export Club, Inc. - "United States Trade and Investment Interests in Latin America", March 12, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 236)
  - Newfoundland, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 237)
  - New York - Ogdensburg, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 238)
  - New York - Staff Paper - Taxation and Finance, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 239)
  - New York - State Insurance, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 240)
  - New York State - Robert S. Bird - Herald Tribune Articles, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 241)
  - New York State - Census - Population, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 242)
  - New York State - Correspondence, 1958-1964 (Box 40, Folder 243)
  - New York State - Department of Agricultural Material, 1956-1958 (Box 40, Folder 244)
  - New York State - Economic Expansion Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 245)
  - New York State - "Facts that call for Action: New York State's Economic Trends", undated (Box 40, Folder 246)
  - New York State - General Electric, 1955, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 247)
  - New York State - Industry Studies, 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 248)
  - New York State - Insurance Department, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 249)
  - New York State - Interdepartmental Committee on Low Incomes, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 250)
  - New York State - Labor Cost Studies, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 251)
  - New York State - Legislation, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 252)
  - New York State - NAR (Nelson A. Rockefeller) Speeches, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 253)
  - New York State - Operating Ratios, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - New York State - Speeches and Articles, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - New York State - Taxes, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 256)
  - New York State - Transportation and Highways, 1958-1959, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 257)